

□ (+1) 647-708-5763 | salimansour@gmail.com | slimnsour.me | slimnsour.me

Summary_

Software Engineering student graduating from the University of Toronto in April 2020. Professional experience specializing in software design, testing, and implementation. Huge video game enthusiast, aiming to be a indispensable asset to a talented development team in the industry.

Work Experience _____

Centre for Addiction and Mental Health

NEUROIMAGING RESEARCH ANALYST

May 2019 - August 2019

- Implemented imaging preprocessing pipelines for neuroscience research and used them to efficiently prepare data for 6 unique studies totalling over 500 subjects.
- · Redesigned large projects in the neuroscience community including dmriprep and Nipype, and created tractography pipeline tractify to decrease generation time from an hour to 15 minutes.

Geosoft Inc.

AUTOMATED TEST ENGINEER

January 2018 - August 2018

- Tested main product Oasis montaj through Ranorex by managing over 1000 tests for each release and reporting results, decreasing the average failure rate for each build by 30%.
- · Presented results in weekly meetings, communicating with coworkers in other departments to boost understanding of automated testing.

Education

University of Toronto

HBSc Specialist in Software Engineering, GPA 3.7/4.0

September 2016 - April 2020

- Achieved UofT Scholars Entrance Award for being among the top 700 students admitted.
- Awarded Dean's List every year for maintaining a high GPA.

Extracurricular Activity

Game Dev Guild

EXECUTIVE

January 2018 - present

· Coordinating with a team to gather resources and plan projects to showcase in weekly meetings, explaining the logic behind popular game mechanics to guide beginners.

Projects.

Balloonatics

GAME DEVELOPMENT

September 2019 - present

· Developing an action platformer, solving experimental programming challenges including seamless level looping and practicing iterative improvement of game feel and user experience.

Ray Tracer

COMPUTER GRAPHICS, UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO

September 2019 - December 2019

 Built a ray tracer in C, combining linear algebra and programming concepts to implement advanced features including multithreading, depth of field, and refraction.

Tractify

NEUROIMAGING PREPROCESSING PIPELINE

May 2019 - August 2019

 Designed and built an efficient tractography generation pipeline using software design principles to greatly decrease runtime, and containerized it using Docker for accessibility and reproducibility.

Languages_

Programming C, Python, C#, C++, Java, R, HTML, SQL, Bash

Testing Ranorex, JUnit, Selenium Game Development Unity, GameMaker:Studio